I'm going to be generous.
And I'm going to assume that those of you who have the nerve to suggest that those of us who see Zoran Mamdani capitulating to the Israeli Jewish population, to the Zionist population as purity politics.
I'm going to assume that you simply don't know that Zionists are racist.
I'm going to assume that you simply don't know that Zionists support the genocide in Palestine.
I'm going to assume that you simply don't know that the Israel lobbies, which include far more than AIPAC, partner with our congresspeople, with our oligarchs in the United States to launder our tax money to make themselves richer.
However, I'm going to assume that you don't know that, which is why you would fix your fingers to type, we cannot have purity politics with politicians.
If you think that expecting someone to simply be the same candidate throughout their election, to simply stand on the same principles they have throughout their election is an example of purity politics.
If that is what you think, if that is what you think, then I want you to know, you are the problem.
You, not the leadership, not the politicians, you.
Because you, the people, have made it acceptable to lack principles, to be flimsy and spineless.
You, the people, have somehow conflated, not supporting genocide as purity.
And nothing ever will change for you until you, the people, change.